Where can we go from His presence?
Where can we go from His presence? Nowhere!
It is time now for His blessing to locate you.
Listen, you have been positioned already.
You have been positioned. - [Amen]
You must believe what I am saying because this is not my word - not mine!
You have been positioned! - [Amen]
For healing! - [Amen]
For blessing! - [Amen]
For deliverance! - [Amen]
For salvation! - [Amen]
Right now, begin to receive it!
Viewers all over the world, begin to receive it!
Receive them right now, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to receive them!
His mercy - you have been positioned!
You have been positioned for His mercy!
His favour - you have been positioned for His favour! - [Amen]
Receive it right now.
I have been positioned for His favour.
I have been positioned for His mercy!
His favour, His mercy - Lord Jesus, in Jesus Christ's name! - [Amen]
I command healing on you! - [Amen!]
Wherever affliction, disease or sickness located - be healed! - [Amen]
Be removed! - [Amen]
Where can affliction go? Where can disease go?
In your organ - there is no hiding place.
In your blood - be healed! - [Amen]
In your bones - be healed! - [Amen]
I can see you being healed! - [Amen!]
I can see you being delivered! - [Amen!]
I can see!
Remember, physical eyes can see the present darkness but the eyes of faith can see the light.
I can see! - [Amen!]
Physical eyes can see the present darkness, your situation, the sickness, disease
but the eyes of faith can see the light. - [Amen]
Be free, in Jesus' name! - [Amen!]
Be free! - [Amen!]
You are free. - [Amen]
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Listen, the devil must remove his hand. - [Amen!]
Listen, Jesus is involved; devil, you must remove your hand! - [Amen!]
When Jesus is involved, devil, remove your hand!
Remove your hand!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
RV: Mel Flowers 20/03/2019